justfalafel.com 2015-03-20

# Just Falafel • Privacy policy

**Website privacy policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.  
·         Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
·         We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
·         We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
·         We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
·         Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
·         We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
·         We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.  
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**What information do we collect?**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to websites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

  **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

  **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  **By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.**
